[
  {
    "front": "montagne",
    "back": "山"
  },
  {
    "front": "rivière, fleuve",
    "back": "川"
  },
  {
    "front": "dessus, haut, lever, monter",
    "back": "上"
  },
  {
    "front": "sous, bas, baisser, descendre",
    "back": "下"
  },
  {
    "front": "centre, milieu, moyenne, dedans",
    "back": "中"
  },
  {
    "front": "important, grand",
    "back": "大"
  },
  {
    "front": "petit",
    "back": "小"
  },
  {
    "front": "an, année",
    "back": "年"
  },
  {
    "front": "aller",
    "back": "行"
  },
  {
    "front": "venir, prochain",
    "back": "来"
  }
]
